let questions23 = [
    {
      numb: 1,
      question: "Aborigine",
      answer: "C. Ureinwohner",
      options: [
        "A. Tourist",
        "B. Künstler",
        "C. Ureinwohner",
        "D. Matrose"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 2,
      question: "to ban",
      answer: "A. verbieten",
      options: [
        "A. verbieten",
        "B. tanzen",
        "C. kochen",
        "D. malen"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 3,
      question: "cautious",
      answer: "D. vorsichtig",
      options: [
        "A. glücklich",
        "B. müde",
        "C. stark",
        "D. vorsichtig"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 4,
      question: "to confess",
      answer: "B. gestehen",
      options: [
        "A. laufen",
        "B. gestehen",
        "C. schlafen",
        "D. singen"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 5,
      question: "cottage",
      answer: "C. Hütte",
      options: [
        "A. Brücke",
        "B. Fabrik",
        "C. Hütte",
        "D. Flughafen"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 6,
      question: "daytime",
      answer: "A. Tageszeit",
      options: [
        "A. Tageszeit",
        "B. Jahreszeit",
        "C. Woche",
        "D. Jahrhundert"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 7,
      question: "desperate",
      answer: "D. verzweifelt",
      options: [
        "A. hungrig",
        "B. reich",
        "C. faul",
        "D. verzweifelt"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 8,
      question: "to fade",
      answer: "B. verblassen",
      options: [
        "A. wachsen",
        "B. verblassen",
        "C. springen",
        "D. fliegen"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 9,
      question: "fierce",
      answer: "C. wild",
      options: [
        "A. ruhig",
        "B. freundlich",
        "C. wild",
        "D. langsam"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 10,
      question: "to gamble",
      answer: "A. wetten",
      options: [
        "A. wetten",
        "B. putzen",
        "C. backen",
        "D. nähen"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 11,
      question: "lawn",
      answer: "D. Rasen",
      options: [
        "A. Dach",
        "B. Wand",
        "C. Fenster",
        "D. Rasen"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 12,
      question: "to mow",
      answer: "B. mähen",
      options: [
        "A. pflanzen",
        "B. mähen",
        "C. gießen",
        "D. graben"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 13,
      question: "outlaw",
      answer: "C. Gesetzlose",
      options: [
        "A. Lehrer",
        "B. Bäcker",
        "C. Gesetzlose",
        "D. Arzt"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 14,
      question: "prospect",
      answer: "A. Aussicht",
      options: [
        "A. Aussicht",
        "B. Geschmack",
        "C. Geruch",
        "D. Geräusch"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 15,
      question: "purse",
      answer: "D. Geldbörse",
      options: [
        "A. Schuhe",
        "B. Hut",
        "C. Mantel",
        "D. Geldbörse"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 16,
      question: "rod",
      answer: "B. Stange",
      options: [
        "A. Tisch",
        "B. Stange",
        "C. Stuhl",
        "D. Bett"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 17,
      question: "seldom",
      answer: "C. selten",
      options: [
        "A. immer",
        "B. oft",
        "C. selten",
        "D. manchmal"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 18,
      question: "to shave",
      answer: "A. rasieren",
      options: [
        "A. rasieren",
        "B. waschen",
        "C. kämmen",
        "D. bürsten"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 19,
      question: "terrified",
      answer: "D. erschrocken",
      options: [
        "A. froh",
        "B. traurig",
        "C. wütend",
        "D. erschrocken"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 20,
      question: "wizard",
      answer: "B. Zauberer",
      options: [
        "A. Bauer",
        "B. Zauberer",
        "C. Fischer",
        "D. Jäger"
      ]
    }
];

export default questions23;